quiz_data = [
        {
            "question": "Which of this is odd ?",
            "choices": ["Queue", "Array", "Linked List", "Stack"],
            "answer": "Array"
        },
        {
            "question": "Which will use the rule of FIFO ?",
            "choices": ["Hash function", "Queue", "Stack", "Linked List"],
            "answer": "Queue"
        },
        {
            "question": "Why python is awesome",
            "choices": ["Readbility and simpilcity", "Extensive libraries", "versatility", "All"],
            "answer": "All"
        },
        {
            "question": "Which of those is The Community whisperer @ALX_SWE ?",
            "choices": ["Julien Barieber", "Irene Aragona", "Obed Ehoneh", "Guillaume salva"],
            "answer": "Irene Aragona"
        },
        {
            "question": "Which is the best suited algorithm for Graph Coloring Problem ?",
            "choices": ["Shortest Path Algorithm", "Sorting Algorithm", "Backtracking", "Kruskal's Algorithm"],
            "answer": "Backtracking"
        },
        {
            "question": "Who is Founder of Holberton School ?",
            "choices": ["Julien Barieber", "Irene Arogan", "Fred Swinkler", "Dennis Ritchie"],
            "answer": "Julien Barieber"
        },
        {
            "question": "Which one of those doesn't exist on the intranet dashboard",
            "choices": ["QA Reviews", "Projects", "Slack", "Discord"],
            "answer": "Slack"
        },
        {
            "question": "Who is Curriculum, Quality & Experience Analyst at ALX ? ",
            "choices": ["Julien Barieber", "Irene Aragona", "Amanuel Sisay", "Obed Ehoneah"],
            "answer": "Obed Ehoneah"
        },
        {
            "question": "Which is not in the curriculum of sprint 1 according to alx_swe ?",
            "choices": ["python Language", "vi and emacs", "C Language", "Shell Script"],
            "answer": "python Language"
        },
        {
            "question": "Which cohort was graduated first @ 2024 ?",
            "choices": ["C-10", "C-11", "C-12", "C-9"],
            "answer": "C-11"
        }
]
# We can add more questions here
